<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keizer Internet</title>
    <link>http://keizerinternet.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Keizer Internet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 20:53:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://keizerinternet.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://keizerinternet.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 20:53:52 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keizerinternet.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Us Send emails about the Keizer Internet Project to keizerinternet@pm.me
Office Hours Dylan &amp;amp; Daniel will be at the Starbucks at 4943 River Rd N every 3rd Tuesday from 6pm to 8pm. Please join us to talk about our goal of a municipal network in Keizer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mission</title>
      <link>http://keizerinternet.com/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 06:48:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keizerinternet.com/mission/</guid>
      <description>Our Mission Empower the citizens of Keizer Oregon to be able to make their own decisions in regards to their internet service providers We believe that the citizens of Keizer know what is best for them and as such, they should have the power to control their internet providers.
Why a Municiple Internet Service Municiple Internet Providers generally offer higher speeds at lower prices. Allowing more of the residents to be connected to the internet empowers more residents of the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://keizerinternet.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 16:01:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keizerinternet.com/about/</guid>
      <description>KeizerInternet.com is the official website for updates on the Keizer Internet project.
The Keizer Internet Project advocates for a free and open internet for Keizer citizens. We believe the best way to ensure a free and open internet is by creating a publicly funded, city-wide network utility service.
The Keizer Internet Project is founded by Dylan Juran and Daniel Miedema. We are citizens of Keizer who are passionate about internet freedom and the internet’s powerful role in our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>