<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keizer Internet</title>
    <link>http://keizerinternet.com/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Keizer Internet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 06:48:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://keizerinternet.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>mission</title>
      <link>http://keizerinternet.com/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 06:48:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keizerinternet.com/mission/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;our-mission&#34;&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;empower-the-citizens-of-keizer-oregon-to-be-able-to-make-their-own-decisions-in-regards-to-their-internet-service-providers&#34;&gt;Empower the citizens of Keizer Oregon to be able to make their own decisions in regards to their internet service providers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe that the citizens of Keizer know what is best for them and as such, they should have the power to control their internet providers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-a-municiple-internet-service&#34;&gt;Why a Municiple Internet Service&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;municiple-internet-providers-generally-offer-higher-speeds-at-lower-prices&#34;&gt;Municiple Internet Providers generally offer higher speeds at lower prices.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allowing more of the residents to be connected to the internet empowers more residents of the community. With internet enabled devices becoming near ubiquitous, internet access is becoming increasingly vital to every day life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;we-can-ensure-we-abide-by-net-neutrality-rules&#34;&gt;We can ensure we abide by Net Neutrality rules&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running our own service for our own residents means we have the power to control how that data is used. We won&amp;rsquo;t need to charge a premium for access to various services. We won&amp;rsquo;t need to aggregate data usage and sell it to advertisers. We are in control of our own data and can ensure the internet is treated just as it should be in this day and age: As a Utility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;common-refutes&#34;&gt;Common Refutes&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-have-choice-in-internet-service-providers-now&#34;&gt;We have choice in internet service providers now&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do, that is correct. However, ask around and you&amp;rsquo;ll get a good sense of the feelings towards our current internet offerings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-choices-we-have-now-seem-fine-though&#34;&gt;The choices we have now seem fine though&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With providers emposing data caps on usage, higher speeds locked behind high premiums, doubious pricing models with short term incentives that lock you in for longer than the good price lasts, and hidden fees sprinkled throughout bills it&amp;rsquo;s hard to get a &lt;em&gt;true&lt;/em&gt; sense of what the real cost of internet is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;billing-can-t-be-that-bad&#34;&gt;Billing can&amp;rsquo;t be that bad&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It tends to vary a lot based on needs, and usage. With higher quality video coming to streaming providers it&amp;rsquo;s easy to cause your internet bill to balloon by streaming too much high quality content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;net-neutrality-doesn-t-concern-me&#34;&gt;Net Neutrality doesn&amp;rsquo;t concern me&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be frank, it should. We don&amp;rsquo;t know what will come with the rules of Net Neutrality slowly being chipped away, but we do know what it would allow providers to do if they did not exist&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charge more for access to video streaming services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charge more for access to Social Networking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charge more for access to News&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sell usage information to advertisers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://keizerinternet.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 16:01:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keizerinternet.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KeizerInternet.com is the official website for updates on the City of Keizer&amp;rsquo;s Muinicpal Internet project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>